let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is metaverse?",
    answer: "Virtual World",
    options:[
    "Virtual World",
    "Hypothetical World",
    "Universe beyond physical world",
    "Real World",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
    question: "What can we do in metaverse?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options:[
    "Get entertained",
    "Work",
    "Socialise",
    "All of the above",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 3,  
  question: "When was the term metaverse first originated",
  answer: "1992", 
  options:[ 
  "1994",
    "1992",
    "1986",
    "1997",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
    question: "Why Metaverse development is important?",
    answer: "To advance virtual reality technology", 
    options:[
    "To advance virtual reality technology",
    "To develop augmented reality technology",
    "To live in VR world",
    " None of the following",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
    question: "Name the access points of metaverse.",
    answer: "All of the above", 
    options:[
    "computers",
    " smartphones",
    " Virtual reality",
    "All of the above",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
    question: "Examples of nfts are",
    answer: "Both A and B", 
    options:[
    "Pictures",
    "Clothing",
    "Both A and B",
    "None of the above",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
    question: "What is the full form of  NFTs?",
    answer: "Non Fungible tokens", 
    options:[
    "Non Fungible tokens",
    "Non Funding token",
    " Non functional technology ",
    "Non formal token ",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
    question: "Which are companies actively participating in metaverse?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options:[
    "Meta",
    "Microsoft",
    "Apple",
    "All of the above",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
    question: "Why nfts are key concepts in metaverse?",
    answer: "A type of Cryptocurrency", 
    options:[
    "A type of Cryptocurrency",
    "A condiment",
    "To explore metaverse",
    "None of the above",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
    question: "Which was the first science fiction novel where term metaverse was originated?",
    answer: "Snow crash", 
    options:[
    "Snow crash",
    "Lava crash",
    "Candy crush ",
    "Lava dash ",
    ]
},
];